<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on y.digital</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on y.digital</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:45:28 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/company/shared-knowledge/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Y.digital Opens New Office in Asia</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/y-digital-opens-new-office-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:45:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/y-digital-opens-new-office-in-asia/</guid><description>Y.digital just opened its 1st office in Asia last month. With this strategic move we are expanding our footprint to the APAC market and growing the team.</description></item><item><title>Smartvoices becomes part of y.digital</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/smartvoices-becomes-part-of-y-digital/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 06:38:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/smartvoices-becomes-part-of-y-digital/</guid><description>Joining forces Conversational AI &amp;amp; Voice AI.</description></item><item><title>Beyond Numbers Words</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/beyond-numbers-words/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 06:03:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/beyond-numbers-words/</guid><description>The value of analysing text</description></item><item><title>Y Acquires Css Motion</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/y-acquires-css-motion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 07:09:56 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/y-acquires-css-motion/</guid><description>Art Ligthart joining as Partner</description></item><item><title>The New Comfort Zone</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/the-new-comfort-zone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/the-new-comfort-zone/</guid><description>Rebecca Wald on the human touch in bots</description></item><item><title>Dr Ian Fitzpatrick Joined Y Digital as Partner CTO</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/dr-ian-fitzpatrick-joined-y-digital-as-partner-cto/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 13:48:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/dr-ian-fitzpatrick-joined-y-digital-as-partner-cto/</guid><description>Ian FitzPatrick joined Y. Digital to drive innovation and growth</description></item><item><title>Humans Supercharged</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/humans-supercharged/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/humans-supercharged/</guid><description>Levering knowledge work using Machine Learning (ML), RPA and Rule Based systems. How to scale unique human qualities**.** A few years ago I was working on a project to deliver a fully automated underwriting process. During this project the term RPA (Robotic Process Automation) came up as ‘a revolutionary way to scale knowledge work’. In all honesty, I had to look up the term RPA as I was a bit intimidated by what it stood for but it turned out to be rather simple 😉 In the years after I have seen much confusion around the topic of scaling knowledge and what method (ML, RPA, Rule based or human insight) is best suited to the needs of a specific business process.</description></item><item><title>Alphabet Soup</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/alphabet-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 21:05:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/alphabet-soup/</guid><description>Until a few years ago computers were lousy at understanding concepts in text or dealing with complex decision criteria.
Opportunities through advances in NLP
Until a few years ago computers were lousy at understanding concepts in text or dealing with complex decision criteria. The capabilities of Natural Language Processing (NLP) have, however, evolved rapidly over the last 10 years providing tangible opportunities to deliver real business value with NLP solutions.</description></item><item><title>Time to Shift the Paradigm</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/time-to-shift-the-paradigm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 21:03:45 +0100</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/time-to-shift-the-paradigm/</guid><description>In the late 90s the field of A.I. fell into disrepute. The promise was evident but the delivery fell well short. The period came to be known as the (first?) A.I. winter. Thanks to rapid improvements in computing capability, abundance of data and a major paradigm shift in A.I. methodology the long winter is now behind us and the impact of A.I. on our daily lives is rapidly becoming manifest.</description></item><item><title>Why Digital Strategies Fail</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/why-digital-strategies-fail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 21:01:04 +0100</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/why-digital-strategies-fail/</guid><description>Digital technology has become an inextricable part of our lives and is rapidly changing our economy and businesses. Every company has developed a digital strategy but many experience difficulties in the execution. McKinsey investigated why so many digital strategies are failing. The article can be found here. A brief summary:
Pitfall 1: Fuzzy definitions Some leaders view digital as an upgraded term for what their IT-functions does. They should however have a broad holistic view of what digital really means for products and services, processes, business models, people and technology.</description></item><item><title>Ai in Law and Legal Practice</title><link>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/ai-in-law-and-legal-practice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 20:57:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>/company/shared-knowledge/blog/ai-in-law-and-legal-practice/</guid><description>Artificial Intelligence has been applied in the juridical domain for several years now. Edgar Alan Rayo researched the current state of AI in legal and wrote an interesting article.
He breaks down AI’s current legal applications into the three categories: applications helping lawyers perform due diligence and research; applications providing additional insights and “shortcuts” through analytics; applications automating creative processes (including some writing) in legal work.
Based on the assessment of current players, he proposes six major categories:</description></item></channel></rss>